{
    "question": "timo:Why didn't Didi want to go home? gerard:his mother ... him for causing the car accident. \u00a0 a.would blame b.blames c.had blamed d.blamed",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Jawaban :\u00a0<strong><br>a. Would blame</strong>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "50-anggota-tubuh-hewan-dalam-bahasa-inggris-dan-artinya-ter-721",
            "question": "50 anggota tubuh hewan dalam bahasa inggris dan artinya ? \u00a0 (Terserah hewan apa)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "wound, leg, nose, mouth, chin, finger, foot, dll<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "nose, eyes, ears, hand, foot, leg, mouth, tongue, stomatch",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tulislah-15-kalimat-mengenai-seorang-chef-116",
            "question": "Tulislah 15 kalimat mengenai seorang chef",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Mr. Anwar is Chef<br>he worked in a restaurant<br>his job was to cook<br>he always works in the kitchen<br>he serves a customer order<br>he wears a white shirt<br>he also wears an apron<br>he&#039;s worked since morning<br>he always maintain the cleanliness of the kitchen<br><span>he usually adds a new menu</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>1.chef is the cook <br>2.chef usually cook food <br>3.chef working in the kitchen for cooking <br>4.chef also worked in restaurant dishes <br>5.chef cook food <br>6.chef like tasting food <br>7.chef cooking for people who buy their food <br>8.chef really like the food and beverage <br>9. chef must be smart <br>10. people who cook like a chef could open his own <span>restaurant<br><br>\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0  Maaf cuma bisa 10 aja .. :) smoga bisa membantu<br><br></span></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-does-a-dog-look-like-what-does-a-cat-look-like-what-does-a-990",
            "question": "What does a dog look like?\r\nWhat does a cat look like?\r\nWhat does a fish look like?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.\u00a0It has fur, four legs, and tail<br>2. It has fur, mustache, four legs<br>3. it has scales and fils",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-dialog-interview-test-dalam-bahasa-inggris-beserta-artiny-509",
            "question": "Buatlah dialog interview test dalam bahasa inggris beserta artinya .",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Excuse me, Sir. May I come in?</span>\n<span>\n(Permisi Pak, Bolehkah saya masuk)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Yes. Please, come in and have a seat.</span>\n<span>\n(Ya, Silahkan masuk dan silahkan duduk)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Thank you, Sir.</span>\n<span>\n(Terimakasih, Pak)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : So, your name is Sinta, right?</span>\n<span>\n(Apakah nama anda sinta, Benar?)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Yes, that is right, Sir.</span>\n<span>\n(Ya, Itu benar pak)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Very well, my name is Alfon. I am the head of the human resource department of this hotel company.</span>\n<span>\n(Baiklah, Nama saya Alfon, saya adalah kepala departemen sumberdaya manusia hotel ini)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Nice to meet you, Sir.</span>\n<span>\n(Senang bertemu anda, Pak)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : How are you this morning, Sinta?</span>\n<span>\n(Bagaimana kabar anda pagi ini,Sinta)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : I\u2019m perfectly fine, Sir. Thank you, and how about you?</span>\n<span>\n(Saya sangat baik, Pak. Terimakasi, bagaimana kabar bapak)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : I\u2019m fine too. Thank you. So, do you know what we are going to do, Sinta?</span>\n<span>\n(Saya juga baik. Apakah anda tahu apa yang akan kita lakukan, Sinta?)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n : Yes, Sir. I was emailed and called by phone in order to have a job \ninterview session from this company three days ago. So, now here I\u2019m \ngoing to be having an interview job session with you.</span>\n<span>\n(Ya,\n Pak. Saya diemail dan ditelepon untuk mengikuti sesi interview \npekerjaan dari perusahaan ini tiga hari yang lalu. Sekarang disini akan \nmengikuti wawancara kerja dengan Bapak)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Very well. Can you tell me about your self, Sinta?</span>\n<span>\n(Baiklah, dapatkan anda\u00a0 menceritakan tentang diri anda?)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n : My name is Sinta Rahmawati. I\u2019m 23 years old. I graduated from one of\n State Universities in Bandung. I took hotel-management as my major. I \nlove travelling and singing. Travelling and singing both improve my \nhealth mentally and physically.</span>\n<span>\n(Nama\n saya Sinta Rahmawati. Umur 23 tahun. Saya lulusan Universitas Negeri \ndai Bandung jurusan Managemen Perhotelan. Saya suka travelling dan \nmenyanyi, travelling dan menyanyi meningkatkan kesehatan mental dan \nfisik saya) \u00a0</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : You applied to be our Junior Hotel Manager. Do you have any experience of this job?</span>\n<span>\n(Anda melamar pekerjaan untuk menjadi Manager Hotel Junior. Apakah anda memiliki pengalaman pada pekerjaan ini?)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : No, Sir. I am a fresh graduate. This is my first time to apply a full time job.</span>\n<span>\n(Tidak pak, saya lulusan baru. Ini adalah pertama kali saya melamar pekerjaan full time)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : What makes you decide to apply for Junior Hotel Manager position?</span>\n<span>\n(Apa yang membuat anda memutuskan untuk melamar untuk posisi Manager Hotel Junior?)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n : I think Junior Hotel Manager is an appropriate job position for me. I\n find it attractive and interesting as well. Due to the hotel-management\n major I took, I\u2019m sure that my skills and talents will be conducive to \nthis company\u2019s success. I can also see a bright future of my career by \njoining this company.</span>\n<span>\n(Saya\n pikir Manager Hotel Junior adalah posisi pekerjaan yang tepat untuk \nsaya. Karena itu saya memilih jurusan managemen hotel. Saya yakin bahwa \nkemampuan dan bakat saya akan mendatangkan keberhasilan perusahaan. Saya\n juga dapat melihat masa depan yang cerah dari karir saya dengan \nbergabung dengan perusahaan ini.)</span>\n<span>\nAlfon\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Very well. So, what is your strength and weakness point?</span>\n<span>\n(Baik, lalu\u00a0 apa kekuatan dan kelemahan anda?)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\n : My strength is my cheerfulness, my carefulness, my strong will to \nlearn new things, and my skill to work under pressures and as a team. My\n weakness is my phobia of dark.</span>\n<span>\n(Kekuatan\n saya adalah kegembiraan saya, kehati-hatian saya, kekuatan saya untuk \nbelajar hal yang baru, dan skill saya untuk bekerja dibawah tekanan dan \njuga bekerja dalam team. Kelamahan saya adalah phobia kegelapan.</span>\n<span>\nAlfon:\n Well, it was a great time to have a little talk with you, Sinta. We \nwill announce the result of your interview in a week. Thank you for \ncoming here.</span>\n<span>\n(Baik,\n ini adalah waktu yang sangat bagus untuk sedikit berbicara dengan ana, \nsinta. Kami akan memberitahukan hasil interview ini dalam satu minggu. \nTerimakasih untuk datang kesini)</span>\n<span>\nSinta\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Yes. Thank you, Sir.</span>\n\n<span>(Terimakasih, Pak)</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "nama-lain-dari-verb-1-verb-2-verb-3-dan-verb-ing-pleasenee-649",
            "question": "Nama lain dari Verb 1, verb 2, verb 3, dan verb-ing Please....Need banget&gt;_&lt;",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "v1 = bare infinitive<br>v2 = past tense<br>v3 = past participle<br>ving = present participle",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "membuat-pidato-bahasa-inggris-tentang-menjaga-kebersihan-lingkung-502",
            "question": "Membuat pidato bahasa inggris tentang menjaga kebersihan lingkungan sekolah",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Assalamualaikum wr wb.<br>and good afternoon<br>The Honourable mothers and fathers who are present in this place<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 first of all I would like say thank to the Almighty God who has given us a good healt so we can join in this nice place.<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 The second time, do not forget I said thank to the our Prophet Muhammad Saw had brought us from the realm of darkness into the lightness<br>In addition, I would like say thank to the audience for allowing me to deliver my speech with the theme of keeping the environment clean<br>well, my beloved brothers and sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Keeping the environment clean is a way and the actions we can do to be able to obtain the beauty and the beauty of the environment, other than that if we always keep the environment around us, our environment will be maintained and healthy so that we can all farthest from various diseases.<br>A healthy environment would be more fun and comfortable to live in the neighborhood of a dirty\u00a0 filled with garbage strewn everywhere.<br>My beloved brothers and Sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 We have seen so many benefits that can be obtained if we keep the environment clean, therefore we as a society that cares about the environment, let us together to preserve the environment around us to look comfortable and cool in the view<br>and always a pleasant environment.</span><span>My beloved Brothers and Sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 So what can I say, if there are sentences that are less pleasing to you, I apologize, because there is no ivory that is not going to crack and there would be no human beings make mistakes.<br>thank you for your attention and wasalamualaikum wr wb.<br></span><span><br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebutkan-20-contoh-makanan-sehat-sebutkan-10-contoh-snak-882",
            "question": "\u221esebutkan 20 contoh makanan sehat    \u221esebutkan 10 contoh\u00a0 snak sehat\r\n\u221esebutkan 10 contoh cemilan sehat \r\n\r\nSEMUA BESERTA GAMBAR NYA ..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "makanan sehat: oatmeal, pepaya, berry, sayuran berdaun hijau, jagung, alpukat, edamame, beras merah, buah pir, brokoli, apel, jambu biji merah, tomat, nanas, mangga, kacang plong, kacang almond, kacang putih, kacang hitam, roti.<br>snack sehat: granola, biskuit gandum, yoghurt, kacang, bubur gandum, sandwich, roti pita,kacang kedelai, tumis sayuran, buah-buahan.<br>cemilan sehat: eskrim, yoghurt, keju, smoothie bluberi, kacang almond, biskuit, agar-agar, pisang, popcorn, brokoli, wortel.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "makanan sehat :<br>1. wortel<br>2. brokoli<br>3. sawi<br>4. kol<br>5. kembang kol<br>6. tahu<br>7. tempe<br>8. kacang panjang<br>9. bayem<br>10. kangkung<br>11. petai<br>12. jengkol<br>13. jagung<br>14. pare<br>15. keju<br>16. tomat<br>17. paprika<br>18. asparagus<br>19. labu siam<br>20. jeruk\u00a0lemon<br><br>snack sehat :<br>1. Taro Snack<br>2. Cheetos<br>3. Piatos<br>4. Chitato<br>5. ChikiBall<br>6. Chuba<br>7. Pringles<br>8. Kusuka<br>9. Qtella<br>10. Lays<br><br><span>10 \u00a0cemilan sehat :<br></span>1. tahu<br>2. tempe<br>3. telur<br>4. daging<br>5. tahu bacem<br>6. tempe bacem<br>8. dendeng\u00a0<br>9. kerupuk<br>10. keripik singkong",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "10-peringatan-di-tempat-umum-dalam-bahasa-inggris-dan-maknanya-479",
            "question": "10 peringatan di tempat umum dalam bahasa inggris dan maknanya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Don&#039;t park = dilarang parkir<br>Don&#039;t stop = dilarang berhenti<br>Don&#039;t turn right = dilarang belok kanan<br>Don&#039;t turn left = dilarang belok kiri<br>no smoking = dilarang merokok<br>Keep silent = diam<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "dilarang berhenti : prohibited stopped<span><br></span>dilarang parkir : parking is prohibited<br>dilarang belok kiri : prohibited left turn<br>dilarang belok kanan : prohibited left right turn<br>hati-hati : caution<br>tikungan ke kanan : bend to the right<br>tikungan ke kiri : bend to the left<br>tanjakan : incline<br>tikungan tajam ke kiri : sharp bend to the left\u00a0<br>tikungan tajam ke kanan : sharp bend to the right",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tuliskan-percakapan-binggris-2-orang-tentang-makanan-indonesia-690",
            "question": "Tuliskan percakapan\u00a0b.inggris 2 orang\u00a0tentang makanan indonesia !",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "waiter : can i take your order please<br>costumer : i would one rice<br>waiter : what do you want to drink with your rice ?<br>costumer : i want a glass tea<br>waiter : would you like anything else ?<br>costumer : i;d like the bill please ?<br>waiter : here you are<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bisa-bantu-gak-verb-2-dari-write-buy-830",
            "question": "Bisa bantu gak?\r\nverb 2 dari:\r\nwrite, buy",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "write = wrote\u00a0<br>buy = bought",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kalo write itu wrote, kalo buy itu bought",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}